So friends, the news which we were eagerly waiting for has
finally come and
yes CR, we are talking about ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company, the company which has
given us returns of more than 500 million rupees in 5 years. And
friends, we will get to see the quarterly results of this company coming in a short while.
Friends, we will see
how are the results of the company, how much is the profit of the company in the revenue of the company,
how did the company manage its expenses
in which way, we will
discuss about all the things, but before that you must
subscribe to a show channel
of this company and what was the total expenditure, so
last year the expenditure of this company is
358000 in legs and CR video the
expenditure of the company has increased from 37000
to 48000, it is around around, in this also we are
seeing a jump of 20%,
within the total expenses of the company also
within the total expenses of the company, nine every com and most
important  The point which is about the company's
total net profit for the period is
how the overall profit of the company has been seen.
Now we have come to the profits of the company
and today you can see the
profit of this company. Okay, now I will
open the profit of my company for you. You can see it
clearly. So the profit of the company
was 31000 rupees, which has
now become 35000 rupees. In other words, there was a
jump of more than 15 to 18%
in the profit of this company, which from
my point of view is definitely
good numbers, you can definitely consider it.
We got good results here in
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company. Overall, a
jump of 20 to 100 percent was seen in the revenue of this company. However, the
growth was not that much
in the expenses of the company as well. And if we look
here, we can see that the
profit of this company is also increasing in a good manner by 15 to 18%.  If you
see it, look, it is
6:30 in the market right now, after the market closes, here are the
company's numbers, we will only
know on Tuesday in
what way the market reacts, but if
your vision is long term, then definitely the
numbers are quite good in all, standard is
visible, otherwise if you like today's
video Banda video,
subscribe to the channel, if you have any other
benefit, please share the video with them, do
not say anything at all, Jai Hind,
thank you.